[
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 2*x^3 - 25*x^2 - 42*x + 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 4) + (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 3*x^3 - 9*x^2 - 15*x + 92"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x*(x^3 + x^2 - 6*x - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x + 4) + (x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 8*x^3 + 8*x^2 - 35*x + 75"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 - 9*x^3 + 36*x^2 + 9*x - 55)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + x^4 - 19*x^3 - 20*x^2 + 52*x - 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 4*x^3 - 7*x^2 + 63*x - 195"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x*(2*x^3 - 9*x^2 + 13*x - 90)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 2*x^4 - 6*x^3 + 61*x^2 - 54*x + 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 3*x^3 + 14*x^2 - 26*x - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 - 4*x^3 - 44*x^2 + 76*x - 31"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 12*x^4 - 3*x^3 - 39*x^2 + 124*x - 54"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 2*x^2 - 26*x + 98"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 7*x^4 - 5*x^3 - 51*x^2 + 64*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 3) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 2*x^3 + 33*x^2 - 14*x - 27"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 9*x^3 + 6*x^2 - 80*x - 120"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 7*x^3 + 6*x^2 + 33*x - 33"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 2) + (x - 1)(x + 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 12*x^3 + 49*x^2 - 60*x - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 4) + (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4*x^3 - 14*x^2 - 42*x + 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 3) + (x + 1)(x - 3) + (x - 5)(x - 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 - 22*x^2 + 62*x + 14"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 5) + (x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4*x^3 - 18*x^2 - 11*x + 264"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x*(2*x^2 + 4*x - 21)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 4*x^3 - 9*x^2 - 3*x - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x + 5) + (x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 6*x^2 + 46*x + 21"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 4) + x(x - 1)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 4*x^4 - 5*x^3 - 28*x^2 + 46*x + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 2) + x(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 9*x^4 + 5*x^3 - 90*x^2 - 255*x - 300"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x*(x^2 - 3*x + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 - 29*x^2 + 34*x + 78)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 3) + x(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5*x^4 - 6*x^3 + 30*x^2 + 28*x - 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - x^4 - 51*x^3 + 19*x^2 + 209*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3) + (x + 1)(x - 1)",
    "answer": "2*x^2 - 7*x + 11"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x + 2) + (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 3*x^3 - 42*x^2 + 74*x + 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 11*x^3 + 28*x^2 - 4*x - 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 2*x^3 - 28*x^2 + 94*x - 320"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x - 1)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 10*x^3 + 32*x^2 - 84*x + 60"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 3*x^3 - 24*x^2 - 69*x + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 4*x^3 - 4*x^2 + 12*x + 10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5) + (x + 1)(x - 5) + (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^3 + 3*x^2 - 18*x - 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "3*x*(x^4 + 3*x^3 - 2*x^2 - 2*x + 12)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 6*x^4 + 4*x^3 - 18*x^2 + 17*x - 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^3 + 4*x^2 - 5*x - 10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 3) + x(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 2*x^3 - 14*x^2 + 73*x - 163"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 2*x^3 - 8*x^2 - 78*x - 93"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 2) + (x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x*(x + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 + 3*x^3 - 20*x^2 - 92*x - 40)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 4) + (x - 2)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 6*x^2 - 13*x - 18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^3 - x^2 + x + 11"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 7*x^4 - 7*x^3 - 52*x^2 - 82*x - 48"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 8*x^4 + 4*x^3 - 71*x^2 - 104*x + 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 3*x^3 + 34*x^2 - 16*x - 176"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 - 4*x^3 - 12*x^2 + 64*x - 64)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2) + x(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 13*x^3 + 26*x^2 - 32*x + 32"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 8*x^4 + 29*x^3 - 44*x^2 + 28*x + 110"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 7*x^4 + 11*x^3 - 6*x^2 - 6*x + 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4*x^4 - 18*x^3 + 108*x^2 - 140*x + 48"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 + 4*x^3 - 10*x^2 - 52*x - 54)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x - 3)(x + 4) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + x^4 - 17*x^3 - 20*x^2 + 17*x + 68"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 7*x^4 - 20*x^3 - 158*x^2 - 123*x - 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 3) + (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 6*x^4 + x^3 + 57*x^2 - 93*x - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3) + (x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 6*x^2 + 11*x - 33"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x + 4) + x(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 10*x^3 + 18*x^2 - 30*x - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 3) + (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "3*x^3 - x^2 - 58*x + 38"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 7*x^2 - x + 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 - 18*x^3 + 24*x^2 + 74*x + 48"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 4) + (x + 1)(x + 5) + (x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 7*x^2 + 28*x + 29"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 2) + (x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 6*x^2 - 13*x - 21"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 3) + (x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + x^3 - 20*x^2 + 3*x - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + x^4 - 14*x^3 + 3*x^2 + 38*x - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x*(x^2 + 3*x - 8)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 4*x^2 - 20*x + 52"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 3) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2*x^4 - 18*x^3 - 13*x^2 + 58*x + 22"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 2*x^3 + 73*x^2 + 10*x + 66"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 14*x^3 - 7*x^2 - 57*x + 120"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 5*x^3 - 56*x^2 - 125*x + 150"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4) + (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 1)",
    "answer": "x^3 + 8*x^2 + 6*x + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 1) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^3 - x^2 - 11*x - 7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 9*x^3 + 7*x^2 + 47*x - 42"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "3*x^3 + 15*x^2 + 48*x + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 1) + x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 + 5*x^3 - 4*x^2 - 23*x + 9)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 8*x^3 + 3*x^2 - 52*x + 64"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 11*x^3 + 16*x^2 + 56*x + 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + (x - 1)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 7*x^3 + 15*x^2 - 7*x - 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 7*x^4 - 8*x^3 - 46*x^2 - 10*x - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3)(x - 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5*x^4 - 5*x^3 + 88*x^2 - 239*x + 394"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 5*x^2 - 14*x - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 6*x^3 - 2*x^2 - 19*x + 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 3) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - x^4 - 60*x^3 + x^2 + 362*x + 48"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 2*x^2 - 25*x - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 10*x^3 + 13*x^2 - 19*x + 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 9*x^4 + 12*x^3 - 3*x^2 - 42*x + 18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4*x^4 + 3*x^3 + 106*x^2 - 91*x + 32"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 5*x^4 - 48*x^3 - 54*x^2 - 26*x - 27"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 3) + (x - 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 25*x^2 + 63*x - 45"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^3 - 6*x^2 + 4*x + 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 2) + x(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 2*x^3 - 27*x^2 + 22*x + 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x - 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + x^3 - 5*x^2 - 31*x + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 8*x^3 + 13*x^2 - 25*x - 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 6*x^4 + 45*x^3 + 273*x^2 - 267*x - 23"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 9*x^3 + 6*x^2 - 9*x + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 12*x^4 + 50*x^3 + 81*x^2 + 36*x - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2) + (x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 11*x^3 + 11*x^2 - 29*x - 90"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4*x^4 - x^3 + 30*x^2 - 49*x + 143"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 5*x^3 - 44*x^2 + 99*x + 80"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "2*x*(x^3 + 3*x^2 - 22*x - 60)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 9*x^4 - 13*x^3 - 215*x^2 - 313*x + 31"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^3 + 5*x^2 + 5*x + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 + 6*x^3 - 12*x^2 - 90*x - 123"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x*(2*x^4 + x^3 - 42*x^2 - 22*x + 135)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2*x^4 - 13*x^3 - x^2 + 27*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2) + (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 13*x^3 + 74*x^2 - 169*x + 110"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2) + (x - 1)(x + 5) + (x - 2)(x + 4) + (x - 5)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^3 - 5*x^2 + 23*x - 48"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "4*x^4 - 2*x^3 - 37*x^2 - 63*x + 26"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3) + (x - 5)(x - 4) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 4*x^3 - 23*x^2 + 72*x + 100"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 2) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x - 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 8*x^3 - 7*x^2 - 84*x + 10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 2) + (x - 4)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 8*x^2 - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 4)(x + 3) + (x - 5)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 8*x^4 + 24*x^3 + 55*x^2 - 84*x - 56"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 8*x^4 + 19*x^3 + 18*x^2 - 108*x + 88"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^4 - 2*x^3 - 11*x^2 - 71*x - 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 2) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2) + (x - 1)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 6*x^4 + 9*x^3 - 13*x^2 + 24*x + 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2*x^4 - 18*x^3 - 4*x^2 + 67*x + 104"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 3*x^3 - 43*x^2 - 24*x + 80"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x*(x^3 - x^2 - x - 14)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 8*x^3 + 22*x^2 + 28*x - 60"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 6*x^2 - 10*x + 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^3 + 11*x^2 + 22*x + 50"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 2*x^2 - 29*x - 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "3*x^3 - 6*x^2 - 36*x + 60"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 5*x^3 - 14*x^2 - 36*x - 66"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4) + (x - 4)(x - 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 8*x^3 + x^2 - 12*x - 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 7*x^4 - 6*x^3 + 128*x^2 - 216*x - 18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4*x^3 - 23*x^2 - 76*x + 70"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 10*x^4 - 13*x^3 + 121*x^2 - 114*x + 14"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 2*x^2 - 5*x + 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3) + (x - 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 2*x^3 + 2*x^2 - 11*x + 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 4*x^4 + 6*x^3 + 100*x^2 + 28*x + 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5) + (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 4) + (x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 6*x^3 - 30*x^2 - 35*x + 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2*x^4 - 20*x^3 - 27*x^2 + 36*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5*x^4 - 20*x^3 + 136*x^2 - 62*x + 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 9*x^4 + 19*x^3 - 8*x^2 - 18*x - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 34*x^3 + 24*x^2 + 267*x - 54"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 + x^3 - 24*x^2 + 24*x + 10)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 2) + (x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 2*x^2 - 34*x - 26"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^4 - 22*x^3 + 33*x^2 + 33*x - 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 - x^3 - 8*x^2 - 26*x + 40)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 6*x^4 - 27*x^3 - 125*x^2 - 71*x - 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 41*x^2 + 33*x + 162"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 2*x^3 - 30*x^2 + 225"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 8*x^3 + 27*x^2 + 10*x - 144"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 25*x^3 + 3*x^2 + 19*x - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 16*x^3 + 28*x^2 - 113*x - 60"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 - 9*x^3 - 61*x^2 + 235*x - 76"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3) + x(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 6*x^3 + 11*x^2 + 43*x + 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 2) + x(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^3 + x^2 - 6*x + 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4) + (x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4*x^4 - 21*x^3 + 66*x^2 + 76*x - 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 5*x^3 - 22*x^2 - 51*x + 23"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 8*x^2 - 15*x - 13"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + (x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^3 - 2*x^2 - 16*x + 44"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 6*x^4 - 25*x^3 - 147*x^2 - 75"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 2*x^4 - 7*x^3 - 5*x^2 + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 - 16*x^3 + 19*x^2 - 57*x - 45"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 - 13*x^2 - 10*x - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 6*x^2 + 10*x - 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "3*x^3 + 10*x^2 + 21*x - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3) + x(x - 1)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 8*x^3 + 27*x^2 - 13*x + 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 8*x^4 - x^3 - 83*x^2 - 34*x + 160"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5) + (x - 1)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^2 - x - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4*x^3 - 13*x^2 - 30*x + 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 - x^3 - 6*x^2 - 5*x - 16)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 - 18*x^3 + 91*x^2 - 37*x - 76"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 5*x^4 - 13*x^3 - 48*x^2 + 42*x + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2*x^4 - 30*x^3 - 47*x^2 + 140*x - 96"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + (x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 2*x^3 - 31*x^2 + 88*x - 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 9*x^3 + 20*x^2 - 9*x - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 6*x^4 + 10*x^3 + 5*x^2 - 8*x - 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 + 5*x^3 - 35*x^2 - 65*x + 94)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "3*x*(x^2 + 5*x + 7)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 13*x^3 + 19*x^2 - 14*x - 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 7*x^3 + 22*x^2 + 56*x - 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 10*x^4 - 3*x^3 - 152*x^2 - 188*x - 48"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 16*x^2 + 37*x + 23"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 + x^4 - 18*x^3 - 43*x^2 - 37*x - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 + 11*x^3 + 6*x^2 - 28*x - 80)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3) + x(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 11*x^4 + 46*x^3 - 124*x^2 + 84*x + 48"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 5) + x(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 6*x^2 - 19*x - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2) + (x - 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 12*x^3 + 25*x^2 + x - 46"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 3*x^4 - 9*x^3 - 11*x^2 - 118*x - 190"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 2*x^4 - 25*x^3 + 27*x^2 + 123*x + 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 4) + x(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^3 + x^2 - 25*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3) + x(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 - 6*x^3 + 15*x^2 - 5*x - 9)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^2*(x + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 8*x^4 + 17*x^3 - x^2 - 22*x - 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 3*x^4 - 17*x^3 - 24*x^2 + 61*x - 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 5*x^3 - x^2 + 15*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 3*x^4 - 19*x^3 - 26*x^2 + 92*x - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 - 4*x^2 + 6*x - 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 2) + x(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 6*x^3 - 15*x^2 - 60*x - 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x - 3)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "3*x^3 + 6*x^2 - 31*x - 21"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 6*x^3 + 5*x^2 + 36*x - 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 8*x^4 - 125*x^2 - 241*x - 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3) + (x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 6*x^4 - 7*x^3 + 90*x^2 - 128*x - 83"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 1) + x(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + x^3 - 2*x^2 + 29*x + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x*(2*x^2 + 9*x - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 3) + (x - 2)(x + 4) + (x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 6*x^4 + 8*x^3 + 17*x^2 + 22*x + 13"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 4) + (x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2) + (x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 10*x^2 + 37*x + 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 5) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 2) + x(x - 5)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 4*x^3 + 4*x^2 - 10*x - 7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 - 5*x^2 + 26*x - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 8*x^3 + 18*x^2 + 3*x - 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 2)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x*(2*x^2 - 2*x - 7)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 3*x^3 + 103*x^2 + 41*x - 130"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 15*x^3 + 21*x^2 + 116*x - 236"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 8*x^4 + 20*x^3 - 14*x^2 + 7*x + 44"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 8*x^3 - 25*x^2 + 59*x + 80"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x - 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 6*x^3 - 17*x^2 - 65*x + 14"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 + 2*x^3 - 27*x^2 - 14*x + 104)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 7*x^4 - 6*x^3 - 111*x^2 - 168*x + 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x*(x^3 - x^2 - 12*x + 30)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 - 4*x^3 - 24*x^2 + 124*x - 97)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 3*x^3 - 28*x^2 + 55*x - 71"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 - 9*x^3 - 37*x^2 + 213*x - 218"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 - 24*x^2 + 65*x + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 4*x^3 - 32*x^2 - 10*x + 144"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 10*x^4 + 37*x^3 + 63*x^2 + 34*x - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2) + x(x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 25*x^4 + 87*x^3 + 145*x^2 + 7*x + 10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 14*x^3 + 5*x^2 + 26*x + 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x*(2*x^4 - 7*x^3 - 25*x^2 + 98*x - 72)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 5*x^3 - 26*x^2 - 109*x + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 5)(x - 2) + (x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + x^3 - 5*x^2 + x + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 7*x^4 - 2*x^3 - 46*x^2 - 20*x - 80"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 + 3*x^3 - 25*x^2 - 46*x + 157)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 5*x^3 - 14*x^2 - 87*x - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 + 2*x^3 - 26*x^2 - 13*x + 98)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 15*x^4 + 8*x^3 - 94*x^2 - 92*x + 45"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 4*x^3 + 22*x^2 + 49*x - 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 4*x^2 + 6*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3) + (x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 16*x^2 + 47*x - 51"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 - 4*x^3 - 4*x^2 + 9*x + 26)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 + 8*x^3 + 21*x^2 + 40*x + 50)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 + 5*x^3 - 4*x^2 - 28*x + 16)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 3) + x(x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 12*x^4 + 39*x^3 - 113*x - 33"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5*x^4 - 13*x^3 + 150*x^2 - 217*x - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^4 - 15*x^3 + 15*x^2 + 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 6*x^4 + 10*x^3 + 6*x^2 - 61*x + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 3) + x(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x*(x^4 - 5*x^3 + 41*x + 31)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x*(2*x^3 + 6*x^2 - 15*x - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 6*x^4 - 27*x^3 - 81*x^2 + 191*x + 276"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 7*x^4 - 21*x^3 + 101*x^2 + 69*x + 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 5)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 - 6*x^2 + 27*x - 43"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 6*x^3 - 27*x^2 - 5*x + 177"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 3) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "3*x^3 - 14*x^2 + 16*x + 6"
  }
]